Michal Nawrocki

Fiolkowa 35, Gliwice 44-109, Silesia, Poland +48 571 447 422

michal.m.nawrocki@gmail.com <u>linkedin.com/in/michal-m-nawrocki</u> github.com/michal-nawrocki www.nawrocki.dev

Profile

Recent Computer Science graduate with +4 years of commercial software development experience. Has a big understanding of software development and a passion for self-improvement. Is ready to tackle any problem and continue his self-taught programming journey. Interested in remote offers for engaging and exciting projects.

Skills

- Fast learner
- Responsible
- Fluent in Polish, English, German
- · Good with managing time
- Open to new experiences
- Creative
- Great with working in teams
- Reliable

References

Michal Domagala

Engineering Manager

Flyr, Cracow, PL

linkedin.com/in/michal-domagala-pl

Interests





Synthwave Music



Reading



Foreign Languages



Sci-Fi Movies





Playing the Guitar

Technical skills

Languages Tools/Platforms Python, JS, TS, Java, JetBrains, VS Code, Git,

SQL, C#, C/C++, Haskell, Docker, Argo, AWS, HTML/CSS, Rust

Kubernetes, PostgreSQL

Main areas of experience

· Object-oriented programming

 Software engineering • Test-driven development • REST APIs

• Dockerization/Containers

Algorithms

• Web services infrastructure

Microservices

Frameworks

FastAPI, Flask,

Flutter

Django, DRF, React,

Education

MSci Computer Science with an Industrial Year // 2016 - 2021 University of Birmingham, UK

Upper Second-Class Honours (2:1, 3.75 GPA)

Master's Project: Implementing a password manager product that uses voice authentication (Written in Python, Flutter and Google Cloud) Noticeable modules: Operating Systems, Networks, Network Security, Mobile computing with Android, Security of Real-World Systems, Algorithms and Complexity, Intelligent Robotics, Functional Programming

International Baccalaureate Diploma Programme // 2013 - 2016 Zespol Szkol Ogolnokstalcacy nr 10 in Gliwice, Poland

Final Mark - 35 out of 45

Noticeable subjects (out of 7): Computer Science HL (6), Mathematics (5)

Work experience

Software Developer // November 2022 - Current

Flyr, Cracow, Poland (remote work)

Responsibilities/Tasks/Duties:

- Extracted components from a monolith-based application into various microservices written in Python
- Improved and expanded Fast API microservices with new functionality
- Worked on implementing PubSub and other Google Cloud services into multiple products
- Took part in designing user-management infrastructure that used Auth0
- Debugged user applications and worked on DevOps tasks that required Docker, Kubernetes and Google Cloud

Software Developer // September 2020 - November 2022 Yobota, London, UK (remote work)

Responsibilities/Tasks/Duties:

- Took part in different projects and PODs (i.e. staff API)
- Improved and expanded Django REST Framework-based microservices with new features and endpoints
- Took part in platform design discussions
- Co-wrote multiple microservices for the company's banking platform

Industrial placement // July 2019 - September 2020 Yobota, London, UK

Responsibilities/Tasks/Duties:

- Expanded features of the company's simulation framework used to predict the behaviour of the in-house banking platform
- · Containerized services using Heroku, AWS, Docker and Ansible
- Wrote Confluence documentation of the codebase